<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2007-2013 Artigile.
  ~ Software development company.
  ~ All Rights Reserved.
  ~
  ~ This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Artigile. ("Confidential Information").
  ~ You shall not disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance with the terms of the
  ~ license agreement you entered into with Artigile software company.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">How is my phone doing?(Beta)</string>
    <string name="show_tutorial">Help</string>
    <string name="unregister">Unregister</string>
    <string name="sample_menu_item">clickMe</string>
    <string name="already_registered">Device has been already registered in GCM</string>
    <string name="server_registering">registering server</string>
    <string name="connecting_to_howismyphonedoing_server">connecting to howismyphonedoing server</string>
    <string name="failed_to_register_device">Failed to register your device, please try later</string>
    <string name="failed_to_unregister_device">Failed to unregister your device, please try later</string>
    <string name="server_registered">server had been registered</string>
    <string name="server_register_error">server registration error</string>
    <string name="server_unregistered">server unregistered</string>
    <string name="server_unregister_error">server unregistered</string>
    <string name="error_config">configuration is incorrect</string>
    <string name="gcm_registered">GCM registered</string>
    <string name="gcm_unregistered">GCM unregistered</string>
    <string name="gcm_message">GCM message</string>
    <string name="gcm_deleted">GCM deleted</string>
    <string name="gcm_error">GCM error</string>
    <string name="gcm_recoverable_error">GCM recoverable error</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="test">Test Button</string>

    <string name="your_device_has_no_linked_google_account_title">Ops!</string>
    <string name="your_device_has_no_linked_google_account_message">It looks like your device does not has linked Google
        account. Please register your device with Google in order to use \"How Is My Phone Doing App\". The application
        will automatically exist when you tap OK
    </string>
    <string name="cleanLogs">Clean Logs</string>
    <string name="testButton">Test</string>
    <string name="device_registered">Device is Registered in Google cloud</string>
    <string name="device_not_registered">Device is not Registered in Google cloud</string>

    <string name="device_admin_label">How Is My Phone Doing Admin</string>
    <string name="device_admin_description">Device administration for better performance and better phone battery.
    </string>
    <string name="device_admin_explanation">By enabling anti-theft feature you\'re can control security sensitive data
        of you device remotely such as change device password, or erase all the data or lock the device and etc.
    </string>

    <string name="admin_receiver_status">Status: %1$ss</string>
    <string name="admin_receiver_status_enabled">anti theft enabled</string>
    <string name="admin_receiver_status_disable_warning">By disabling this you won\'t be able to perform AntiTheft
        features of How Is my Phone Doing App remotely from a web site. You can always enable it back from the app.
    </string>
    <string name="admin_receiver_status_disabled">anti theft disabled</string>
    <string name="admin_receiver_status_pw_changed">pwd changed</string>
    <string name="application_website_url">http://ioanbsu.com</string>
    <string name="application_start_message_title">WARNING</string>
    <string name="application_start_message" formatted="false">
        <![CDATA[
<div style="font-weight:bold;font-size:20px;">PLEASE READ THIS FIRST!!!</div>

        <b>How to delete the application?</b>
        Below instructions about how to delete this application.
        <ul>
            <li>If you decided to enable AntiTheft feature and set this application [How Is My Phone Doing?]
                as Active Device Administrator, then before deleting it you should first remove [How Is My Phone Doing?]
                app from the list of device administrators: Settings-> Security -> Device Administrators -> Uncheck
                checkbox next to [How Is My Phone Doing?] app
                <br/>
                After that you can remove application regular way you do it on your device
            </li>
            <li>
                If you did not enable AntiTheft feature you can remove the application the same way as you remove any
                other application on your device
            </li>
        </ul>
    <b>How to use this application?</b>
    <ul>
        <li>After launching this application go to %1$s</li>
        <li>Log in on web site your google plus account</li>
        <li>Make sure that you use the same account to log in on %1$s and on your android device</li>
        <li>Right after logging in to %1$s the application automatically will start search for your devices. The
            location detection is
            slow process and sometimes may take long time. If you realize that your device(s) can not be found for long
            period of time, click
            <i>Update Devices Location</i> button to force location detection to be executed again
        </li>
        <li><b>To send message</b> click on <i>Send message</i> button, fill in all the required fields and click <i>Send
            message</i> button inside appeared window
        </li>
        <li><b>To see device status information and update device settings, or use AntiTheft feature</b> click <i>My
            Devices(*)</i> button and select device you want to check in left list panel
        </li>
    </ul>
    <b>Why I can not see any devices on %1$s?</b>
        There are several reasons why you may not see your device on %1$s website.
        If you don\'t see any devices on %1$s, please try doing following:
        <ul>
            <li>
                Make sure that you android device has access to the internet
            </li>
            <li>Make sure that after closing whit window you see green label at the top of the screen saying that <i
                    style="color:green;font-weight: bold;">%2$s</i></li>
            If you see <i style="color:red;font-weight: bold;">%3$s</i> that means
            there is a problem registering device into Google Cloud Messaging system. To fix this please try to restart
            the application. If restarting the application does not help, please send the problem description to
            ioanbsu@gmail.com
            <li>Check that google account name that you\'ve logged in with to %1$s (displayed at the top right
                corner in %1$s) the same as
                your google account name that you use ont you android device. To check the google account name that is
                used on your device, please close this window and
                read the text in green at the top of you device\'s screen. it will have information about what account is
                used by [How Is My Phone Doing?] app
            </li>
            <li>Try to refresh %1$s website</li>
            <li>If nothing described above helped, please contact the application owner with detailed problem
                description
                at ioanbsu@gmail.com
            </li>
        </ul>

    <b>Why am I always seeing this message when I start the application?</b>
        <ul>
            <li>
                People tend to think that this application
                is a virus because after enabling AntiTheft feature they can not delete the application. Well this is
                not true,
                the reason why this application can not be removed once the AntiTheft feature is enabled is because of
                Android OS
                policies. Once the AntiTheft feature enabled the [How Is My Phone Doing?] app marked as device
                administering app.
                According to Android OS policies it is impossible to remove device administering applications from
                Android OS.
                So to remove this app it should we first unchecked as device administering app. After that it can be
                easily removed.
            </li>
            <li> Main purpose of this application is to provide control of your phone/tablet from the web site %1$s
            The [How is My Phone Doing?] application should be started only once to register itself in Google Cloud Messaging
            system. And after that there is no sense of starting and stopping this application - it is already registered
                in cloud and can be controlled from the website %1$s . The only reason to open this application
                would be to see instructions that are displayed in this popup.</li>
        </ul>

        ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="remote_application_url">http://howismyphonedoing.appspot.com/remoteService</string>
    <!--<string name="remote_application_url">http://169.229.196.12:8080/remoteService</string>-->
    <string name="enableAntiTheft">Enable AntiTheft</string>
    <string name="antitheft_enabled_text">You had enabled AntiTheft feature on you device. That means you will be able
        to wipe out you phone\\tablet remotely(when it stolen) or lock the screen with new pin code that you enter on
        ioanbsu.com. Also Beware, that by enabling AntiTheft feature you marked [How Is My Phone Doing?] application as
        administrative application for you device. That means that you won\'t be able to remove [How Is My Phone Doing?]
        application from your device unless you remove administrative rights from [How Is My Phone Doing?] app. You can
        do so in your device\'s settings.
    </string>
    <string name="device_registered_info_text">You can open now https://ioanbsu.com on your computer\'s favorite browser
        to control your device online. Log in using the same Google account name that you use on this device: %1$ss
    </string>


</resources>
